剧情回顾...
你有没有想过  他们把你丢在这里
Did you ever think, maybe they put you down here
让你每108分钟按一次按键
to push the button every 108 minutes
只是为了看你是否会乖乖照做所有的这一切
just to see if you would... and all of this
每天都要这样
Evey single day.
你在珍珠舱内的任务会持续三周
You two's duty in the proof of last way which
在此期间  你和你的同伴
and during this time you and your partner
会观测到一个正在进行的心理学实验
will observe a psychological experiment in progress
我可怜的生命的每一秒钟
Every single second of my pathetic little life
就像那个按键一样的无用
is use these buttons.
如果你不继续按按键了  John...
If you will not continue to push the button, John...
我来按
I will.
我写了四个名字
I've write four mames down.
四个你朋友的名字
Four of your friends.
如果你没有把名单上的人都带来
If you don't bring all of the people on the list,
你就再也见不到Walt了
you will never see Walt again.
Walt?
爸爸 别离开我
Dad, don't leave me.
我会带你离开这里的
I will keep out of you .
爸爸  我爱你
Dad, I love you.
我也爱你  Walt
-I love you too. Walt.
Michael?
-我想Michael向他们妥协了  -他为什么要骗我们?
-I think Michael was compromised.  -Why would he deviced us?
因为我相信他要带你们去一个陷阱
Because I belive he is leaving you in a trap.
我必须带回我的孩子
I have to get my son back.
我们会帮你的  Michael
I will help you do that. Michael.
但是必须按我说的做  伙计
But it's gotta be the way I said, man.
你  我  Kate  Sawyer  Hurley...就这些人  -那好吧
You, me, Kate, Sawyer, Hurley...that's it.  -Then that's the way it'll be.
船
Boat.
-我们得救了?  -我们获救了?
-We are rescued?  -We are saved?
你看到什么了么?
You see anything?
没有
No.
也许是圈套
Maybe it's a trap.
你是什么意思  圈套?
What do you mean, a trap?
听见了么?
You hear that?
该死
Damn it!
是你
You.
声明: 本字幕由YYeTs美剧字幕组原创翻译制作
欢迎访问官方论坛  www.YYeTs.net 在线观看 剧情讨论 学习交流
=====本字幕由以下成员荣誉制作 感谢他们的无私奉献======
翻译：Singa校对： BillSky
后期：xyz 双语制作：DrunkBat
========== 字幕总监制：七色九天 ==========
那么  在你离开之前
So... before you ran off
我想你忘了提起
I guess you just forgot to mention
你还有艘帆船
that you still have a sailboat.
你为什么回来?
Why'd you come back?
你以为我是故意的么?
You think I did it on purpose?
我船开了一个半礼拜了
I was sailing for two and half weeks
以九节的速度向西开
bearing due west and making nine knots.
不到一周我就应该到达斐济了
I should've been in Fiji in less than a week.
但是我看到的第一个陆地不是斐济
But the first piece of land I saw wasn't Fiji, was it? No.
不是的  是这里  这个...
No, it was here. This...
这个岛
this island.
你知道为什么吗?
And you know why?
因为就是这了
Because this is it.
这里就是唯一的了...
This is all there is left.
这个大海和这个岛屿
This ocean and this place here.
我们被粘在这个该死的地方了
We are stuck in a bloody snow globe!
这是个与世隔绝  不可能逃离的地方
There's no outside world. There's no escape.
那么... 那么走开好么  让我喝几杯
So just... just go away. Let me drink.
你们还在按按键么?
Are you still pushing it?
是的  我们还在按
Yeah, we're still pushing it.
放钥匙的
Set of keys.
一个金怀表
One pocket watch, gold-plated.
一张照片
One photograph.
一本书  "我们共同的朋友"
One book: Our Mutual Friend.
你为什么不带这本书进去?
Why didn't you bring that inside?
为了不被诱惑  伙计
To avoid temptation, brother.
我读了所有
I've read everything
查尔斯·狄根斯先生的作品...
Charles Dickens has ever written.
每本书里  每个奇妙的单词
Every wonderful word. Every book
除了这本
except this one.
我留着以后看
I'm saving it.
这会成为我死前读的最后一本书
So it will be the last thing I ever read before I die.
好主意
Nice idea.
你还有很长时间才会死
As long as you know when you're gonna die.
Desmond David Hume下士
Lance Corporal Desmond David Hume
你的刑期结束了
your sentence is hereby complete
你被女皇所有的
and you are now and forever
苏格兰皇家军队永久除名
dishonorably discharged from the Royal Scots Regiment of Her Majesty's Armed Forces.
女皇万岁
Long live the queen.
好好看你的书去吧
Enjoy your sodding book.
想搭便车么?
You want a ride?
不想跟你坐
Not with you.
上车
Get in the car.
你给我带礼物了么?
Did you bring me a present?
事实上是两件礼物
Actually, two presents.
一个盒子装了你的过去
One of these boxes contains your past, Hume.
另一个装着你的未来
The other, your future.
来吧  打开它
Go ahead. Open it.
你这混蛋  你知道么?
You're a bastard, you know that?
她从来没有得到你的...关爱
The fact that she never received your...sentiments
你的关爱对她来说是好事...
Your sentiments is good for her.
因为她所知道的
Good because, as far as she's concerned,
是你抛弃了她
you've forsaken her.
而且她一直这么以为
And that's the way it's going to stay.
现在也是么?
Is it now?
Penelope已经开始新生活了  Hume
Penelope's moved on, Hume.
她要结婚了
She's getting married.
这是为了让你离开我的女儿  开始新生活而准备的
This is for your new life, away from my daughter.
条件很简单
The conditions are simple.
不要再联系了
No contact.
不能打电话  不能写信
No calls. No post.
你只要... 离开她  Desmond
You just... run away, Desmond.
你为什么认为我会离开她?
And what makes you think I would just run away?
因为你是个懦夫
Because you're a coward.
在去葬礼的路上
On the way to the funeral
我告诉过你Michael已经向其他人妥协了
I told you that Michael had been compromised by the Others.
然后你问我怎样才能有所防备
And then you asked me how we might take advantage of that.
我想命运已经给我们答案
I believe fate has given us our answer
那艘船
The boat.
那艘船?
The boat?
Michael带你去的营地...
This camp Michael is leading you to across the island,
他们会在那里设陷阱
that is where they will set their trap.
当Michael从岛上带你们去的时候
While Michael leads you by land
我可以从水上过去
I can approach far more quickly by sea
我能靠岸且不被发现
and I can go ashore undetected.
靠岸后做什么?
Go ashore and do what?
先侦查一下  他们的人数和位置
Scout them. Their numbers and positions.
还有他们的武器
Their weapons.
然后我会去最近的一个海滩
Then I'll go to the nearest beach
用这些来点起烽烟
and start a signal fire with these.
他们烧起来会产生暗黑色的烟
They burn with a dark black smoke.
你和你的队员就朝信号来找我吧
You and your team will come to meet me at the signal
我们就可以一起去了
and we will go in together.
我们还无法确信Michael已经背叛了我们
We're not even sure if Michael's been turned by them.
他已经背叛了
He has been turned by them.
我得去告诉Kate  Hurley还有Sawyer...
I'll have to tell Kate and Hurley and Sawyer what we're doing...
不  不能让Michael察觉他的谎言被看穿了
No. Michael cannot sense we know he is lying.
我们需要的就是出其不意  Jack
All we have is the element of surprise, Jack.
现在  就要靠你来
Right now, it's only your responsibility
保守秘密了
to keep it secret.
黑烟  是么?
Black smoke, huh?
这次...
This time...
他们就会知道黑烟是代表我们来了
they will know that we are coming.
你好  John
Hello, John.
你去哪了?
Where have you been?
我一直在思考
I've been thinking.
思考什么?
About what?
在一分钟之内
That in a minute
电脑就会发出蜂鸣声
that computer's gonna start beeping.
你不要做什么  就随它去
And when it does, you're gonna let it go.
你就让时间变为零  到零以下去
You're gonna let it run down to zero, past zero
你不要去按按键
and you're not gonna push the button.
但是我就要去按按键
But I am going to push the button.
为什么我不呢?
Why wouldn't I?
因为你不想成为一个奴隶
Because you don't want to be a slave.
我不是任何人的奴隶
I am a slave to nothing.
你是这台电脑的奴隶
You're a slave to that.
就像以前的我一样
Just like I was.
我再和你说一次
So I'm gonna tell you again
...别按
...don't push it.
别和我说什么我不该做
Do not tell me what I can't do.
你不能按按键
You cannot push that button!
不  那不是真的
No, it's not real!
我们只是个木偶  吊线木偶
We're only puppets! Puppets on strings!
只要我们按按键  我们永远都不会自由
As long as we push it, we'll never be free.
那你现在自由了  John
Well, you're free now, John.
别再回来
Do not come back.
不
No.
不用了  我拿了它就会杀人
No way. If I take that, I'm gonna kill someone.
我们不就为了这个么?
Ain't that the point?
我想我们是为了把Walt带回来
I thought the point was to get Walt back.
怎么了?
What's the matter?
我们在另一个舱内找到的...
All that stuff we found in the medical station.
服装  化妆品  假胡子
Costumes, makeup, fake beards.
会不会是这些人想让我们觉得他们是山里人?
What these people just want us to think they're hillbillies.
听着听着  我去过那里
Listen. Listen, I was there.
我看见过他们  他们就是山里人
I saw them. They are hillbillies.
他们住的是棚屋  吃的是鱼
They live in huts. They eat fish.
他们可能比我们还要害怕
They're probably more scared than we are
而且他们不知道我们要过去
and they have no idea we're on our way.
好的
All right.
好了  伙计  我们走吧
Enough jibber-jabber. Let's roll.
我需要你的船
I need your boat.
我不会浪费你的时间  外面什么都没有 伙计
I wouldn't waste your time. There's nothing out there, pal.
我不出海
I'm not going out there.
我要快点去岛的北岸
I need to get to the north shore, and quickly.
去看敌人  是么?
Off to see the hostiles, are you?
什么?
The what?
你知道么?
You know what?
眼不见为净
Ignorance is bliss.
船是你的了  伙计
The boat's all yours, brother.
祝你好运
For all the good it'll do you.
我不懂怎么航海
I don't know how to sail.
那我建议你找个懂的
Then I suggest you find someone who does.
给我来一个
Just give me
咖啡因很足的  伙计
whichever one has the most caffeine in it, brother.
该死...
Ah, damn.
抱歉  我刚到这里  并且...
I'm sorry, I've just arrived
我把所有美元都用在出租车上了
and I spent all my American money on a taxi.
算我的
I've got it.
不用了吧
That's not necessary.
只是四块钱
It's just four bucks.
我想你没有四万两千块吧?
I don't suppose you have 42,000 more of those, do you?
就要看用来干什么了
Depends on what it's for.
开个玩笑
I was joking.
不是吧
No, you weren't.
一个单人环球船赛?
A solo sailing race around the world?
我有八个月时间来达到最佳状态
I've got eight months to get into the best shape of my life.
但我告诉你  小姐
But I'll tell you what, miss.
我要赢
I'm going to win.
如果你赢了你会得到什么?
And what do you get if you do?
最重要的是...
What really matters...
我从谁这里赢
is who I win it from.
Charles Widmore
他想花钱让我离开
He tried to buy me off
如果我不拿他的钱
and when I didn't take his money
他就带走我在这个世界上
he took away the only thing in the world
唯一真正关心的人
that I ever truly cared about.
她是谁?
Who is she?
他的女儿
His daughter.
我和她有好些地方配不上
I was unsuitable on several levels.
那么你要四万两千块钱干吗?
And what's the 42 grand for?
有些复杂
It's a wee bit complicated.
到现在为止  我还没有船
As of yet, I don't actually have a boat.
抱歉  我说错什么了么?
Sorry, did I say something wrong?
我有船
I have a boat.
是我丈夫的  但是...
It was my husband's, but...
他得了场病  并且...
he got sick, and...
他想开船去地中海
He wanted to sail to the Mediterranean
但是他没能做到...
but he never...
他死了...
He passed away...
大约一个月前
about a month ago.
我很难过
I'm sorry.
我想把船给你
I want you to have it.
我...我不能要你的船  小姐
I...I can't take your boat, miss.
但是你必须要
But you have to.
他也希望你要
He'd want you to.
你丈夫叫什么名字?
What was your husband's name?
David
他把船取名什么?
And what did he name his boat?
Elizabeth
他用我的名字给船取名的
He named it after me.
那么...
Then
我谢谢你  Elizabeth
I thank you, Elizabeth.
我会赢下这次比赛...
And I shall win this race...
为了爱
for love.
能让我们单独谈谈么?
Would you excuse us, please?
我在岸边等
I'll be at the shore.
Sayid想让你开船去岛的另一面
去帮助Michael
不
我不会离开你的  至少现在不会
你不会离开我的  Jin
因为我要跟你一起去
别碰它
Don't even think about it.
是个陷阱
It's a trap.
一个网  Rousseau在岛上所有地方都安放了
A net. Rousseau's got 'em all over the island.
你怎么知道的?
How the hell would you know that?
我和Jack被网起来过
I kind of tripped one with Jack.
我们最后...
We ended up...
别提了
Never mind.
怎么了?
What?
当医生告诉我说你们被网住了
When the doc told me you all got caught in a net
我以为他是说...
I thought he meant...
其它的什么
something else.
从什么时候开始你和Jack谈起我来了?
And since when did you and Jack start talking about me?
那只鸟是在叫我的名字么?
Did that bird just say my name?
是的  它叫了...
Yeah, it did...
在它压了金块作赌注前
right before it crapped gold.
抱歉  可能我忘了装弹药了
Sorry, man. I guess I forgot to load that one.
John?
你的脸怎么了?
What happened to your face?
没事  我很好
Nothing. I'm fine.
如果你感到少许不安
...if you're feeling a little sorry for yourself
你...你也许想喝点什么
you may want to have a drink
和你舱子里的伙伴一起
with your mate from the hatch.
我听说他也很沮丧
I hear he's a little despondent as well.
什么?
What?
对了  你当时不在场
Oh, that's right. You weren't there
在葬礼上那出戏剧性的回归场面
for the dramatic arrival at the funeral.
我想他按了太多次的按键
I think he's pushed your buttons too many times
是的  Desmond
Yeah, Desmond.
我肯定你们两个有很多好谈的
I'm sure you two have a lot to talk about.
如果我没说清楚我很抱歉  但是...
I'm sorry if what I said was confusing, but...
我只叫Jin和我一起去
I asked Jin to come.
你需要一个翻译
You need someone to translate
而且你需要至少两个懂得航海的人
and you need at least two people who know how to sail.
-Desmond全是靠自己航海的  -那你看他现在的样子
-Desmond managed by himself. -And look where he ended up.
你在浪费时间
You're wasting your time, sister.
我每隔九天注射那个东西
I shot myself with that stuff every nine days
一直持续了三年
for three years.
他很可爱
He's lovely.
他...他父亲也在这个岛上么?
Is the... is the father here on the island?
不  他很早以前就走了
Nope, he's been gone a long time.
就是走了
Just sort of walked off the moment
他对当时的情况感到害怕
he got a bit scared by the situation.
也许他知道他当不好父亲
Well, maybe he knew he'd be a lousy dad.
看来他是为你好
Thought he was doing what was best for you.
他是为他自己好
He was doing what was best for him.
你怎么找到我的?
How did you find me?
你的房东告诉我你每天来这跑步...
Landlord at your flat told me you ran here...
你怎么找到我的?
How did you find me?
我有很多钱  Desmond
I have a lot of money, Desmond.
有钱又有决心  你可以找到任何人
With money and determination, you can find anyone.
你读了你心爱的书了么...
Did you read your beloved book?
那本你留着的书?
The one you were saving?
还没有
Not yet.
我以为你走了的时候读过它了
I thought you might have read it while you were away.
我被关进了监狱
I was in prison.
不是走了
Not away.
你为什么不给我写信?
Why didn't you write to me?
你准备什么时候结婚  Pen?
When are you getting married, Pen?
我们还没定日子
We haven't set a date yet.
我一年后回来
I'll be back in a year.
如果你现在就回来呢?
What if you were back right now?
我一定要赢得这场比赛  Pen...
I'm going to win this race, Pen.
他的比赛
His race.
一年后
And in a year
我就回来了
I'll be back.
Desmond  你这是为了什么?
Desmond, what are you running from?
我要赢回大家对我的尊敬
I have to get my honor back...
我就是为了这个
...and that's what I'm running to.
那么一个雪人对另一个雪人说了什么?
So, what did one snowman say to the other snowman?
闻起来像胡萝卜
Smells like carrots.
你好  Desmond
Hello, Desmond.
你好  做箱子的
Hello, yourself, Box Man.
不介意吧?
Do you mind?
你喝吧
Oh, I insist.
那么你是修好了电脑了?
So you managed to fix the computer then, did you?
世界不是还没被毁么?
The world's still here, ain't it?
我不是太确定  伙计
I'm not so sure about that, brother.
让我想想  Desmond
Refresh my memory, Desmond.
你说你在舱子里呆了多久了?
How long did you say that you were down there in the hatch?
三年
Three years.
Desmond  如果我告诉你...
Desmond, what if I told that... for all that
全部的那三年
all those years
你和所有的以前在那里的人
that you and all the men before you
按那个按键...
were down there pushing that button...
如果我告诉你那都是没有意义的...
What if I told you it was all for nothing?
我问你
I'd ask you how the hell
你怎么知道这些的?
did you know something like that.
我找到了另一个舱子
I found another hatch.
岛上的另一个站点
Another station on the island.
他们叫它珍珠
They called it The Pearl.
我在那看了影片...东方公司的影片...
And I saw a film there. An orientation film
它说
and it said
我们舱子里发生的所有事...
that everything that was happening in our hatch...
都是假的
wasn't real.
只是一个试验
That it was a test.
一个心理试验
A psychological experiment.
你在骗人
You're lying.
想走走么?
You want to take a walk?
我来准备爆米花
I'll make the popcorn.
如果你那么肯定那不是真的
If you're so sure it's not real,
那就别按按键了啊
then just stop pushing the button.
我不幸被排除在外了
I have, except, unfortunately
有另外的人来按了
someone else decided to start.
所以你要冷静点
So you're gonna sober up.
我们晚上好好睡一觉
And we're gonna get a good night's sleep
明天我们去找出如果不按按键
and tomorrow,we're gonna find out what happens
会发生什么
if that button doesn't get pushed.
伙计  要吃的么?
Dharma NutraBar?
不  谢谢  我不饿
No, thanks. I'm not hungry.
你没开玩笑吧?
You serious?
你还好吧?
You all right?
是的  只是想多捡点木材点火
Yeah, just getting some more firewood.
还不够热
Not feeling too hot.
你不应该独自出来的
You shouldn't be out here alone.
-我帮你吧 -好的
-I'll... I'll give you a hand. -Yeah.
谢谢你们为了我的孩子而冒险
thanks for coming out here, risking your neck for my boy.
同生独死  伙计
Live together, die alone, man.
是的
Yeah.
跟你说了要你别来
我不是晕船  Jin
有个东西你来看看
不知是哪个更让人不安...
I don't know what is more disquieting
雕像的其它部分没了...
the fact that the rest of the statue is missing
还是它只有四个脚趾
or that it has four toes.
8...7...6...
Eight. Seven. Six.
5...  4...  1...
Five. Four. One.
John
干的漂亮
Neat trick.
你能听见么?  开门
Can you hear me? Open up!
我希望你能确信这件事  伙计
I hope you're sure about this.
这件事我比任何事都要确信
I'm more sure about this than anything in my entire life.
别这么干  John
Don't do this! John!
那么好吧  做箱子的
All right then, Box Man.
我们在这等
We wait.
你是他么?
Are you him?
一个雪人对另一个雪人说了什么?
What did one snowman say to the other?
你在说什么?
What are you talking about?
你是谁?
Who are you?
我叫Inman
I'm Inman.
Kelvin Inman
我的...
What...
我的船怎样了?
what happened to my boat?
我发现你被冲上了海滩
I found you washed up on the beach.
不过没看到有船
There was no boat.
你这是在做什么?
What was all that about, then?
拯救世界
Just saving the world.
在试验开始后不久
Not long after the experiments began, however,
发生了一件...意外
there was... an incident.
从那时开始
And since that time
就制定了下面的方案
the following protocol has been observed.
每隔108分钟
Every 108 minutes
就要按一下按键
the button must be pushed.
从警报声开始起
From the moment the alarm sounds
你有四分钟时间向电脑里
you will have four minutes to enter the code
输入数字
into the micro-computer processor.
你还要看几遍?
How many times you gonna watch that thing?
为什么有部分没了?
Why are there missing parts?
Radzinsky做了剪辑
Radzinsky made some edits.
谁是Radzinsky?
Who's Radzinsky?
我的搭档
He was my partner.
他怎么了?
What happened to him?
记得你看完了把它
Just make sure you put that back
放在"螺旋桨的转动"那本书后面
behind Turn of the Screw when you're done with it.
你为什么穿那套衣服?
Why do you wear that suit?
这样在外面我就不会被感染了
So I don't get infected out there.
每隔九天给自己注射一下
Give yourself a shot of this every nine days.
在我找到你之前你在外面有段时间了
You were out there a while before I found you.
希望现在注射不是太晚
I hope it's not too late.
做箱子的... 在外面敲门的那个人是谁?
Who is he, Box Man? The man out there pounding on the door.
他叫Eko先生
His name is Mr. Eko.
为什么Eko先生一直带着
Why does Mr. Eko carry around
一根刻有经文的棒子?
a stick covered in scripture?
因为他是一个牧师
Because he's a priest.
快开门  求你了  别这么做
Open the door, please. Don't do this.
John  能听见么  快开门
John! Can you hear me? Open up!
我们把一个牧师锁在了外面?
We locked out a priest?
John
Charlie  你知道他们怎么把舱门打开的么?
Charlie, do you know how they got the hatch door open?
不知道  不过如果你哼个调子 我可能可以弹奏出来
No, but if you hum it, I could probably play it.
他们怎么打开的? 那个写有"检疫隔离"的舱门
How did they open it? The door that says "quarantine".
他们炸开的  怎么了?
They blew it up. Why?
Charlie  我需要你的帮助
Charlie, I need your help.
现在你需要我了  神父?
Oh, now I'm back in your good graces, Father?
Charlie  John把我关在舱子外面了
Charlie, John has locked me out of the hatch
我相信他之所以这么做
and I believe he is doing this because
是因为他不想去按按键
he is going to stop pushing that button.
并且Charlie  我绝对肯定
And Charlie, I am absolutely certain
如果他成功了  在90分钟以内
that if he is successful in 90 minutes
岛上所有的人都会死
everyone on this island will die.
好吧  我帮你
All right, I'm in.
谢谢
Thank you.
来吧  快点
Come on, quick.
那么这些其它人...
So these Others
是达摩组织留下的么?
you think they're left over from the Dharma folk?
我不知道  伙计
I don't know, man.
我的理解?  他们是外星人
My theory? They're aliens.
所以他们用假胡子...
That's why they use the fake beards.
他们的头是塑料做的
Their heads, made of plastetic.
你读错音了  伙计
Prosthetic, dude.
你根本不会拼写  现在倒来纠正我了?
You can't even spell, and now you're correcting me?
你怎么认为  小妞?
What do you think, Freckles?
一直走  我们被跟踪了
Just keep moving, we're being followed.
什么?
What?
继续保持笑容
Just keep smiling.
他们至少有两个人  在河对面
There's at least two of them across the river.
大约五秒钟后  我就要行动了
In five seconds, I'm gonna turn the tables on them.
-那个  等等  -你也来么?
-Well, wait a second.  -You in?
他要逃了
He's getting away.
他死了
He's dead.
-我们得找到另外一个  -不
-We have to find the other!  -No.
-我要去  Sawyer...  -我说了不
-I'm going. Sawyer...  -I said no!
你疯了么? 让他逃了他们就会知道我们来了
Crazy? They'll know we're coming.
-他会通知他们...  -这和我们抓不抓他无关了
-He'll warn them.  -It doesn't matter if we catch him now.
他们已经被通报了
They've already been warned.
你是什么意思  被通报了?
What do you mean, "warned"?
-你为什么不说话  Michael?  -Jack...
-Why don't you tell them, Michael?  -Jack...
-我不知道你在说什  -别装了
-Don't know what you're talking about.  -Stop lying!
告诉他们
Tell them.
告诉他们什么?
Tell them what? I...
我知道你在做什么了  Michael
I know what you're doing, Michael!
现在告诉他们实情
Now, tell them the truth!
-Jack...  -快说
-Jack. -Tell them!
我只能这么做
It was the only way.
他们给了我一个名单
They gave me a list.
什么名单?
What list?
上面有你们的名字
It had your names on it.
我得把你们四个全部带回那里
I had to bring all four of you back
不然他们说我就再也见不到我的儿子了
他们是谁?
Who are they?
就像我说的
It is like i said.
他们...他们住在棚屋里  而且...
They live in a camp with huts, and...
我发誓就是这样
I swear, that's it.
你放走了Henry?
You let Henry go?
你杀了他们?
Did you kill them?
Ana Lucia...
还有Libby?
and Libby.
是么?
Did you?
我不得不这么做
I had to.
我...呃...
I...  uh...
我找不出其它方法
I couldn't find any other way
而且Libby是我误杀的
and Libby was a mistake.
我...我没时间考虑
I didn't have time to think.
但是如果你有时间考虑...
But if you did have time...
你还是会杀了她的  是么?
...you still would've killed her, right?
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
你明白么?  我很抱歉
You understand, I am sorry.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
我...
I...
这是关于我儿子的事情
It's my son.
我要回去了
I'm going back.
不  Hurley
No, Hurley.
Hurley  你不能回去
Hurley, you can't.
我们会被杀的  这你早知道的
We're gonna get killed. You knew it
但你还是让我们来了
and let us come anyway.
现在回去太迟了  Hurley
It's too late to go back now, Hurley.
我们已经发现他们在跟踪我们了
We caught them following us once.
如果他们发现我们不相信Michael了
If they don't believe we trust Michael
他们会把我们全杀了
they'll kill us all.
我很抱歉我没和你们说明
I'm sorry that I didn't say anything.
但是你们得知道如果我没有想好计划
You have to know that I would never bring you out here
我是不会把你们带出来的
if I didn't have a plan!
什么计划?
What plan?
Sayid
看那边
There.
那就是Michael描述的石头了
That's the rock Michael described.
我们到了
We're here.
==============|  YYeTs字幕组招募启示  |==============
英文字幕录制(居住在加拿大和美国)  双语字幕校正   时间轴调整
英语翻译   欧美影视新闻翻译  影视评论  论坛版主  美工人员
服务器提供者  发布宣传  联系地址：www.YYeTs.com
==== YYeTs属于网络爱好者组织 加入者仅凭个人兴趣爱好 无报酬 ====